A Finding Aid to the Holger Cahill Papers, 1910-1993, bulk 1910-1960, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Works Progress Administration Federal Art Project, 1934-1970; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 10.75 Linear feet Boxes 2-14, 18, MMs009
  - General Subjects, circa 1934-1943, 1953; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0682-0728)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0417-0430)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0729-0733)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0431-0479)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0734-0740)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0748-0754)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0480-0488)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0741-0743)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0746-0747)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0744-0745)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0755-0766)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0489-0493)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0767-0789)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, circa 1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0798-0803)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0790-0797)
    - Draft Operating Manual of Museum Services and Education Aids, circa 1935-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0581-0615)
    - Employment Figures, 1935-1936, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0383-0422)
    - Employment Figures, January-March 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0423-0453)
    - Employment Figures, April-December 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0454-0480)
    - Employment Figures, 1937-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0481-0507)
    - Employment Figures, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 1031-1032)
    - General Files, undated; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 340)
    - General Files, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0558-0559)
    - General Files, undated; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0665-0667)
    - General Files, circa 1934-1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 0093-0245)
    - General Files, circa 1935; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0282-0292)
    - General Files, circa 1935; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5288, Frame 0247-0400)
    - General Files, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 0401-0574)
    - General Files, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0401-0416)
    - General Files, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0822-0853)
    - General Files, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 5288, Frame 0575-0804)
    - General Files, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0569-0601)
    - General Files, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 0805-1117)
    - General Files, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 1118-1243)
    - General Files, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0606-0615)
    - General Files, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0873-0889)
    - General Files, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 1244-1520)
    - General Files, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0657-0664)
    - General Files, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0004-0227)
    - General Files, circa 1935-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0557-0580)
    - General Files, circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0229-0260)
    - General Files, 1942; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0645-0654)
    - General Files, 1942; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0542-0552)
    - General Files, circa 1942-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0890-0977)
    - General Files, circa 1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0261-0362)
    - Lists of Projects, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1120-1128)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1023-1065)
    - Notebook, FAP Region 3, Southern, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1405-1493)
    - Report, National WPA/FAP: Summary and Recommendations for Continuation, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0975-1086)
    - WPA/FAP and Negro Art, 1938-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0616-0635)
    - WPA/FAP, Criticism of, 1936-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0636-0645)
    - WPA/FPA, Support of, 1936-1939, undated; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 0939-0941)
    - WPA/FPA, Support of, 1936-1939, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0646-0666)
    - WPA/FPA and War Effort, 1940-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0667-0784)
  - Artist Files, 1935-1943; 3.2; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains records relating to FAP artists. Correspondence is primarily between Cahill and various artists and includes letters of recommendation written by Cahill. General records include a typescript of an interview with Edith Halpert of Downtown Galleries, a document containing case studies on the "Adjustments of Individuals" during FAP work in Michigan; and printed material. A notebook entitled "Artists Whose Loan Assignments Have Been Completed," records "loans" of artists to various states and cities in order to work on FAP projects.
    All individual artist files contain a biographical sketch of the artist, unless otherwise noted. Some files also contain photographs of the artist, as indicated.
    - Artist Files, Correspondence, 1935-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0038-0098)
    - Artist Files, General Records, 1935-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0001-0021)
    - Artist Files, Lists of Artists and Works, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1173-1266)
    - Artist Files, Notebook "Artists Whose Loan Assignments Have Been Completed,", 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0099-0157)
    - Abbott, Berenice, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1268-1270)
    - Barela, Patrocino, circa 1935; Archival Resource Key; (resume) (Reel 1107, Frame 0022-0026)
    - Bennett, Gwendolyn, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1271-1272)
    - Bird, Elzy J., undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1273-1274)
    - Brown, Samuel J., undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Brown) (Reel 5287, Frame 1275-1279)
    - Bufano, Beniamino, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1280-1284)
    - Bufano, Beniamino, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (catalog) (Reel 1107, Frame 0027-0037)
    - Cervantez, Pedro, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Cervantez) (Reel 5287, Frame 1285-1287)
    - Curtis, Phillip C., undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1288-1289)
    - Evergood, Philip, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Evergood) (Reel 5287, Frame 1290-1292)
    - Gershoy, Eugenie, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1293-1294)
    - Gettens, Rutherford J., undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1295-1296)
    - Gorky, Arshile, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1297-1298)
    - Gregory, Waylande, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1299-1303)
    - Guglielmi, Louis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1304-1305)
    - Hiler, Hilaire, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1306-1307)
    - Hord, Donal, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1308-1309)
    - Hunter, R. Vernon, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1310-1311)
    - Jacobi, Eli, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1312-1313)
    - Knaths, Karl, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1314-1315)
    - Kopman, Benjamin, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1316-1318)
    - Macdonald-Wright, Stanton, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1319-1322)
    - Murray, Hester Miller, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1323-1325)
    - Newell, James Michael, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Newell) (Reel 5287, Frame 1326-1329)
    - Olds, Elizabeth, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Olds) (Reel 5287, Frame 1330-1333)
    - Palo-Kangas, John, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Palo-Kangas) (Reel 5287, Frame 1334-1336)
    - Park, Paul, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Park) (Reel 5287, Frame 1337-1338)
    - Quirt, Walter, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes phot of Quirt) (Reel 5287, Frame 1339-1343)
    - Rourke, Constance, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5287, Frame 1344-1345)
    - Segal, George, undated; Archival Resource Key; (photo of Segal only; see also Box 18) (Reel 5287, Frame 1346-1348)
    - Seltzer, Leo, undated; Archival Resource Key; (photo of Seltzer only) (Reel 5287, Frame 1349-1351)
    - Siporin, Mitchell, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Siporin) (Reel 5287, Frame 1352-1357)
    - Sommer, William, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Sommer) (Reel 5287, Frame 1358-1362)
    - Speck, Walter E., undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Speck) (Reel 5287, Frame 1363-1368)
    - Sutton, Harry H., undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Sutton) (Reel 5287, Frame 1369-1372)
    - Trentham Eugene, undated; Archival Resource Key; (typescript by and photo of Trentham) (Reel 5287, Frame 1373-1377)
    - Velonis, Anthony, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Velonis) (Reel 5287, Frame 1378-1382)
    - Viviano, Emmanuel, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Viviano) (Reel 5287, Frame 1383-1386)
    - Ward, Lynd, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Ward) (Reel 5287, Frame 1387-1390)
    - Weisenborn, Rudolph, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Weisenborn) (Reel 5287, Frame 1391-1395)
    - White, Francis Robert, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of White) (Reel 5287, Frame 1396-1399)
    - Wolff, Robert Jay, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Wolff) (Reel 5287, Frame 1400-1404)
  - Administration of the National WPA/FAP, 1935-1942; 3.3; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries includes detailed financial records, memoranda, organizational charts and plans, and reports documenting the administration of the FAP at the national level.
    A file relating to the 1939 changeover includes a typescript by George Biddle, Memorandum on a Post-War Reorganization of the Section of Fine Arts and Other Federal Art Projects, and a reprint of Art Under Five Years of Federal Patronage, also by Biddle.
    Reports consist pimarily of progress reports provided by Cahill and Thomas C. Parker in addition to several general reports written by Cahill, scattered field trip reports, and miscellanous documents providing general accounts of the activities of the FAP.
    General memoranda and program descriptons contain questionnaire results, descriptions of FAP programs, typescripts containing general program descriptions (possibly given as speeches or issued as press releases), and related news clippings.
    Summaries of WPA art programs includes five copies of a document, "The WPA Art Program - A Summary," with hand-written notations updating the information in the Summary through 1942.
    - 1939 Changeover and After, 1939-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0113-0210)
    - Financial Records, Vouchers for Per Diem, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0154-0249)
    - Financial Records, Vouchers for Per Diem, 1942-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0250-0280)
    - Financial Reports, Allotments and Encumberances, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0319-0333)
    - Financial Reports, Analysis of Expenditures, 1935-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0358-0389)
    - Financial Reports, Financial Summaries, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0390-0394)
    - Financial Reports, State Directors of Finance and Statistics, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0356-0357)
    - Financial Reports, Status of Art Project, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0334-0355)
    - Memoranda, 25% Non-Relief Exemptions, 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0001-0112)
    - Memoranda, General, and Program Descriptions, 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 1171-1328)
    - Memoranda, Sponsorship, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0306-0318)
    - Organization Charts, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 1088-1092)
    - Organization Plan, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 1093-1170)
    - Reports, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 1329-1446)
    - Reports, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0560-0568)
    - Reports, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0504-0508)
    - Reports, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 1447-1552)
    - Summaries of WPA Art Programs, 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0211-0305)
  - Administration of the State WPA/FAP, 1935-1943; 3.4; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains records documenting the adminstration of the FAP at the state level. It includes general correspondence and memoranda regarding state activities as well as reports of state program operations and accomplishments, field trip reports, and newsletters and bulletins from state art centers organized alphabetically by state.
    This subseries contains a second set of state studies which, in addition to administrative reports, includes reports representing research and writing conducted as part of the FAP work done at the state level. The second group of reports is also arranged alphabetically by state, and then chronologically, and includes social studies conducted by members of the Federal Writers Program.
    - Correspondence, 1935-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0395-0417)
    - Field Trip Reports, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0804-0807)
    - Lists of State and Regional Directors, circa 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0808-0821)
    - Memoranda to State and Regional Directors, 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0127-0145)
    - Memoranda to State and Regional Directors, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0104-0126)
    - Memoranda to State and Regional Directors, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0076-0103)
    - Memoranda to State and Regional Directors, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0065-0075)
    - Memoranda to State and Regional Directors, Requisitioned Material, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0146-0153)
    - Midwest Mural Competition, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0506-0516)
    - California, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0978-0989)
    - California, circa 1935-1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0418-0513)
    - Florida, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0514-0522)
    - Illinois, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0862-0865)
    - Illinois, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0523-0530)
    - Iowa, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0859-0861)
    - Iowa, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0531-0537)
    - Kansas, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0538-0540)
    - Kansas, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0854-0858)
    - Minnesota, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0532-0538)
    - Minnesota, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0541-0550)
    - Minnesota, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0554-0562)
    - Missouri, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0539-0557)
    - Missouri, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0551-0553)
    - New York City, 1935-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0563-0594)
    - New York State, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0701-0737)
    - North Carolina, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 595)
    - Oregon, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0596-0601)
    - Pennsylvania, circa 1935-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0602-0612)
    - Texas, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0613-0617)
    - Virginia, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0618-0625)
    - Wyoming, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0626-0654)
    - Arizona, The Phoenix Art Center by Morsell, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0364-0372)
    - California, [ Young California Artists] by Morsell for Parnassus, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0373-0377)
    - California, The Hand-Writing on the Walls by Homer W. Evans, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0378-0389)
    - California, The Study of Early American Wall Painting in Southern California by Warren W. Lemmon, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0390-0400)
    - California, Redwood Sculpture on the Federal Art Project, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0401-0402)
    - California, Children's Art Classes by Vivian Swelander, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0403-0409)
    - California, An Exhibition for Artists and Layman Behind the Scenes in Making a Mosaic, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0410-0413)
    - California, An Exhibition That Graphically Demonstrates the Use of Art in Public Buildings, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 414)
    - California, Aquatic Park Exhibition, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0415-0422)
    - California, [ Beniamino Bufano], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0423-0425)
    - California, Sculpture Produced on Federal Art Project of the WPA, California, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0426-0427)
    - California, Southern California Creates, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0428-0455)
    - California, Federal Art Project, Los Angeles Museum, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0457-0461)
    - California, [ Federal Art Project], 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0462-0465)
    - California, Report from the Northern California Project, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 472)
    - California, Transcript of Interview Was There A Mission Style of Design? with Frank Freidel and Warren W. Lemmon, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0466-0471)
    - California, Folk Arts in California From 1769 to 1846 by Marjorie Evelyn De Bord, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0473-0555)
    - California, Federal Art Project Reviews Accomplishment, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0556-0557)
    - California, Untitled, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 558)
    - California, Calfornia's Medical Story in Fresco, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0559-0574)
    - California, Historical Murals in the Los Angeles County Hall of Records Board of Supervisors Hearing Room, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0575-0601)
    - California, Southern California Art Project, Los Angeles Museum, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0602-0611)
    - California, Federal Art Project, [1940]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0612-0616)
    - California, Southern California Art Project, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0617-0629)
    - District of Columbia, The Works Program, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0630-0634)
    - District of Columbia, National Exhibit of Children's Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0635-0638)
    - District of Columbia, The Federal Art Project: A Summary, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0639-0644)
    - Florida, Autobiographical Sketch by Eve Alsman Fuller, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0645-0648)
    - Florida, Financial Report of Federal Art Galleries of Florida, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0649-0650)
    - Florida, Jacksonville WPA Art Center Brochure, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0651-0658)
    - Florida, Report on the History of the FAP in Florida, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0659-0707)
    - Illinois, Cotton Mather by M. R. Bevier, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0708-0724)
    - Illinois, The Centennial Exposition of 1876 by Helen Sikuta, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0725-0806)
    - Illinois, Early Clockmakers in the United States by Oscar Bluhme, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0807-0823)
    - Illinois, Swiss in Chicago Prior to 1900 by Albert Rudin, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0824-0828)
    - Illinois, Polish Emmigration by Stanley Mazur, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0829-0849)
    - Illinois, English Settlement, Edwards County, Illinois, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0850-0854)
    - Illinois, Moravian Brethren by Helen Sikuta, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0855-0883)
    - Illinois, Early Textiles of the Mormon Pioneers by E. J. Bird, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0884-0886)
    - Illinois, Notes on Coverlets, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0887-0897)
    - Illinois, Early American Copper, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0898-0901)
    - Illinois, Mural America by Increase Robinson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0902-0917)
    - Illinois, Applied Arts Report, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0918-0958)
    - Illinois, Bishop Hill Paintings by Archie Thompson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0985-0988)
    - Illinois, Bishop Hill Colony by Ingegerd Linden, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0970-0984)
    - Illinois, Bishop Hill Biographies by Unidentified Author, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0989-1008)
    - Illinois, Bishop Hill, Illinois, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (includes 5 photos of the town) (Reel 5289, Frame 0961-0969)
    - Illinois, Suggestions For Material and Its Location in Illinois, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1010-1016)
    - Illinois, WPA Sculptors Lift Chisels to a 2 1/2 Hour Day, Press Digest, August 19, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1017)
    - Illinois, Condensed Statistical Report Covering Mural Project in Illinois, October 27, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1018)
    - Illinois, Stencilled Walls by William L. Warren, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 0959-0960)
    - Illinois, Bishop's Hill by Holger Cahill, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1009)
    - Illinois, Project Officials Hail Illinois Art Show at Federal Gallery, February 15, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1019-1022)
    - Illinois, The Illinois Art Project, [1939]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1023-1029)
    - Illinois, Baseball In Old Chicago, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1030-1070)